Consumers' League of New York City Records 5307
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Child Labor - 'Berrypicking' Bills - Legislative Sessions, 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Child Labor - 'Berrypicking' Bills Legislative Sessions, 1957-1960 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Includes printed bills and related correspondence
- Child Labor - CL Policy Statements, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Child Labor Committee, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Child Labor - Dangerous Farm Machinery - Legislative Session, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Includes printed bill and correspondence to editors of newspapers
- Child Labor - Dangerous Farm Machinery - Legislative Session, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Child Labor - Dangerous Farm Machinery -Legislative Sessions, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Includes correspondence re bills before Legislature
- Child Labor - Casual Employment and Babysitters and Minimum Age, 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Includes Legislative Bulletins, correspondence re bills before Legislature
- Child Labor - Temporary State Commission to Study, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Children's Aid Society of Buffalo Letter re experimental school of migratory farm workers' children, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Citizen's Committee for Children of N.Y.C., Inc. Includes correspondence re legislation, 1956-1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Citizen's Committee for a Just Settlement of Hospital Strike, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Citizen's Committee on the Fair Labor Standards Act Correspondence, Bulletings, reports, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Citizen's Committee on the Fair Labor Standards Act Bulletins and literature, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Citizen's Union, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Includes correspondence re experimental summer school for migrant children
- Commonwealth of Puerto Rico - Department of Labor, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Includes correspondence re employing foreign agricultural workers
- Community Service Society, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Congressmen - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Consumer Counsel to Gov. Harriman, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Contacts, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Includes lists, correspondence
- Councils of Social Agencies and Community Chests, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Crosby Leaflet, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Includes drafts and printed copies of 'End Feudalism On the Farms' and related correspondence
- Cusack, Eleanor - Fund, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Includes list of contributors and related correspondence
- Cusack, Eleanor - Meetings, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Includes correspondence re arrangements for speeches around N.Y.S.
- Democratic State Committee, 1951-1959 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Disability Insurance - Bills Introduced in the State Legislature, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Disability Insurance - Bills Introduced in the State Legislature, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Disability Insurance - Consumers League Material Includes report, testimony, statements, 1947-1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Disability Insurance - Other States, 1948-1952 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Diocese of Central New York, 1954-1956 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- East Side Cooperative Council, Syracuse, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Education Department, N.Y.S., 1955-1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Includes reports, correspondence
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce Correspondence, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Employment Agencies, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Equal Pay - Miscellaneous Material, 1944-1951 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Includes publications, release
- Facts for Farmers, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Includes three issues
- Fair Labor Standards Research Committee, Inc. (FLSRC) Advisory Committee, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Includes correspondence re disability insurance, lists of committee members
- FLSRC - Disability Insurance Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- FLSRC - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Routine correspondence and proposal for study of N.Y.S. Disability Benefits Law
- FLSRC - Fund Raising, 1949-1958 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- FLSRC - Minutes, 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- FLSRC - Project Designs, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Farm Organizations, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Federal Interdepartmental Committee on Migratory Labor, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Former Board Members, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Governor's Office - State of New York, 1954-1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Includes correspondence between Governor's Office and CL
- Graphic Letter Service (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Routine correspondence re letterhead, etc.
- Health Department - N.Y.S., 1952-1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  correspondence, reports
- Homework - N.Y.S. Legislation and Orders, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Hospital Workers Project, 1947-1950 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Hotel Trades Council, 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Includes statement, correspondence, news releases
- Inquiries, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Includes requests for publications and other correspondence
- Interdepartmental Committee on Farm and Food Processing Labor - N.Y.S., 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Includes correspondence, statements, list of members
- Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1953-1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Includes correspondence, statements, agenda, release
- Joint Legislative Committee on Migrant Labor (Waters Committee), 1955-1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Includes correspondence
- Lawrence, Morton B., 1958 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Includes legislative report, correspondence
- Lease, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Letters to the Editor, 1953-1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Lewis H. Latimer Progressive Association, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Libraries, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Migrant Camp Conditions - Affidavits, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Migrant Camp Study Committee Suggested recommendations (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Migrant Farm Labor, Rochester Meeting, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Feb. 25, 1954 Routine correspondence
- Migrant Survey, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Camp Reports
- Migrant Survey, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Child Labor Carrier Reports
- Migrant Survey, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Child Labor Farm Visit Reports
- Migrant Survey, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Reports
- Migrant Survey, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Sample Questionnaire
- Migrant Labor - Miscellaneous Material Publications, 1945-1957 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Migrant Labor - Bibliographies and Directories, 1950-1956 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Migrant Labor - Survey, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Camp Questionnaires
- Migrant Labor - Camp Visits, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Summer 1958 Includes observation forms, correspondence
- Migrant Labor - Children Publications, 1946-1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - Ad Hoc Conference, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Fall 1957 Includes correspondence and reports
- Migrant Labor - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor - Correspondence, Misc., 1955 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - Publications, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor Committees - Miscellaneous, 1954-1960 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor - Camp Visits, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor - Crew Leaders Survey results, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - Children - Education Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Report and correspondence
- Migrant Children's Fund, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Form letter
- Migrant Labor - Employment Security Publications, 1951-1954 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor - 'The Community Looks At Migrant Labor' - Distribution and Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Migrant Labor - Films and Plays, 1951-1959 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Migrant Labor - Foreign Migrants Publications, 1950-1957 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Migrant Labor - Growers, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Migrant Labor - Housing - Federal Bills and Programs, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Migrant Farm Labor - Sanitary Code, 1948-1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Includes publications, correspondence
- Migrant Farm Labor - Social Security Publication, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - Housing, 1949-1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Includes survey and publication
- Migrant Labor - Housing, 1955-1958 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Includes printed bills, statements, correspondence
- Migrant Labor - International Association of Government Labor Officials, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor - Labor Laws Publications, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - Legislative Action (Peterson Bill), 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Includes correspondence and drafts of bills
- Migrant Labor - Legislative Action, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor - Legislative Action, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor - Legislative Action, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Migrant Labor - Legislative Action, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Migrant Labor - Legislative Action, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor - Mexican Farm Labor Program, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - New York State - Drafts of Legislative (Howard Robinson, N.Y.S. Labor Department), 1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Dec. 1958
- Migrant Labor - N.Y.S. - Erie County Health Dept., 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor - N.Y.S. - Government Reports - Health Department Monthly Gamp Reports, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor -N.Y.S. - Government Records -Health Department Monthly Camp Reports, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - N.Y.S. Government Reports -Interdepartmental Committee, 1947-1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor - N.Y.S. - Government Reports - Joint Legislative Committee on Migrant Labor, 1953-1959 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor - N.Y.S. - Government Reports Migrant Child Care Program, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor - N.Y.S. - Suffolk County Includes report, 1952-1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - Publication, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - California, 1947-1955 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Includes publications, 1947-55
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Colorado, 1951-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Includes publications, 1951-58
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Delaware, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Florida, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Hawaii, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Maryland, 1953-1959 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Michigan, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Minnesota, 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - New Jersey, 1944-1959 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Oregon, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Pennsylvania, 1953-1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Puerto Rico, 1955-1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Texas, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Washington, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor - Other States - Wisconsin, 1950-1956 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - Productivity, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor - Study of Legal Status of Grower and Crew Leader, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor - Summer Schools for Children, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  Includes publication
- Migrant Labor - Survey, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  Summer 1959
- Migrant Labor - Testimony of Stetson Kennedy Before U.N. Ad Hoc Committee on Forced Labor at Geneva, Switzerland, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  7-Nov-52
- Migrant Labor - Transportation, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  Correspondence re legislation
- Migrant Labor - Unemployment Insurance, 1953-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Includes publications
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Agriculture Department Publications, 1950-1958 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Council of State Governments, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Employment Security Exchange - Farm Labor Edition, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Employment Security Exchange - Farm Labor Edition, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Health, Education and Welfare Reports, 1952-1959 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Interagency Committee on Migrant Labor, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Interdepartmental Committee on Children and Youth, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Joint Committee on the Economy Report, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - Labor Dept., 1949-1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor - U.S. Government Reports - President's Committee on Migratory Labor, 1955-1960 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor - Waters Committee Bills, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor - Waters Committee Hearings, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor - Waters Committee, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  Reports and Correspondence
- Migrant Labor - 'Wetbacks' Script for CBS Radio Program, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor - Workmen's Compensation, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor Project - Camp Observation Reports, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor Project - Child Labor Publications, bibliography, 1942-1950 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor Project - Copyright for 'Sweatshops In the Sun' Includes pamphlet, forms and correspondence, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Migrant Labor Project - Correspondence - Florence Kelley, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Migrant Labor Project, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Correspondence re Migrant Labor Farm Study
- Migrant Labor Project - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor Project - Eleanor Cusack's Speaking Engagements, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor Project - Education Publications, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor Project - Employment Service Interviews Questionnaires, interviews, Vol. 1, Ho. 1. of 'Farm Labor Bulletin', 1951 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor Project - Service Material Release, publications, memos, 1950-1952 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor Project - Findings and Recommendations, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor Project - First Annual Conference of the National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor Programs, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  Report, summary, publication
- Migrant Labor Project - Foreign Workers Publications, form letter, notes re Puerto Rican farm workers, 1950-1952 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor Project - Interviews with Gamp Managers Completed questionnaires, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor Project - Interviews with Camp Owners Completed questionnaires, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor Project - Interviews with the Public Notes, interviews, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor Project - Interviews with Workers Completed questionnaires, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor Project - List of Camps - N.Y.S, Health Department, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor Project - Material from Mrs. Nicely Reports, correspondences, 1948-1951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor Project - N.J. Information Statements, notes, publications, 1945-1952 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor Project - N.Y.S. Health Department Semi-Monthly Reports on Farm and Food Processing Labor Camps, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor Project - Letters Commending 'Sweatshops in the Sun', 1952 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor Project - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1950-1954 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Migrant Labor Project - Pamphlet Distribution -Civic, Church, Labor and Welfare Groups, 1952-1953 (Box 29A, Folder 1)
- Migrant Labor Project - Pamphlet Distribution - Growers, 1952 (Box 29A, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor Project - Pamphlet Distribution -N.Y.S. Legislature, 1952 (Box 29A, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor Project - Pamphlet Distribution -State Government Officials, 1952 (Box 29A, Folder 4)
- Migrant Labor Project - Pamphlet Distribution -U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1952 (Box 29A, Folder 5)
- Migrant Labor Project - Bulletin on Peterson Bill, 1953 (Box 29A, Folder 6)
- Migrant Labor Project - Progress Reports, 1951 (Box 29A, Folder 7)
- Migrant Labor Project - Project Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 29A, Folder 8)
- Migrant Labor Project - Project Outline, 1951 (Box 29A, Folder 9)
- Migrant Labor Project - Publicity, 1952-1953 (Box 29A, Folder 10)
- Migrant Labor Project - Questionnaires from Mrs. Nicely and CL Study-, 1946 (Box 29A, Folder 11)
- Migrant Labor Project - Bequest for Waters Committee Investigation of Enforcements, 1960 (Box 29A, Folder 12)
- Migrant Labor Project - Research Report, 1953 (Box 29B, Folder 1)
  Includes drafts of report
- Migrant Labor Project - Special Fund Raising Committee, 1952 (Box 29B, Folder 2)
- Migrant Labor Project - Studies for President's Commission, 1950 (Box 29B, Folder 3)
- Migrant Labor Project - Tables on Crew Leaders Various charts, 1951 (Box 29B, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage Correspondence, Publications, 1921-1946 (Box 29B, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage - Amusement and Recreation, 1951-1959 (Box 29B, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage - Amusement and Recreation - Hearings, 1950-1958 (Box 29B, Folder 7)
- Minimum Wage - Amusement and Recreation - Report and Recommendations, 1950 (Box 29B, Folder 8)
- Minimum Wage - Amusement and Recreation - Surveys, 1950 (Box 29B, Folder 9)
- Minimum Wage - Beauty Service, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage - Beauty Service - Hearings, 1947-1952 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage - Beauty Service - Report and Recommendations, 1947-1952 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage - Beauty Service - Survey, 1936-1951 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage - Building Service, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage - Building Service - Hearings, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage - Building Service - Reports and Recommendations, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Minimum Wage - Building Service - Surveys, 1951-1955 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Minimum Wage - Cleaning and Dyeing, 1947-1957 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Minimum Wage - Cleaning and Dyeing - Hearings, 1947-1952 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Minimum Wage - Cleaning and Dyeing - Report and Recommendations, 1947-1952 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Minimum Wage - Cleaning and Dyeing - Surveys, 1938-1951 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Minimum Wage Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage Committee, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage Committee - Confectionery, 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage - Confectionery - Hearings, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage - Confectionery - Report and Recommendations, 1947-1951 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage - Confectionery - Survey, 1937-1950 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Minimum Wage - Consumer's League Briefs, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Minimum Wage - C.L. Policy Statement, 1946-1960 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Minimum Wage - Exemptions - Western Union, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Minimum Wage - Explanation and Analysis of Fair Labor Standards Amendments, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Minimum Wage - Federal, 1955-1960 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Minimum Wage - Hotel, 1947-1958 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Minimum Wage - Hotel - Hearings, 1947-1958 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Minimum Wage - Hotel - Reports and Recommendations, 1940-1958 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage - Hotel - Surveys, 1938-1956 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage - Laundry, 1952-1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage - Laundry - Hearings, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage - Laundry - Report and Recommendations, 1933-1952 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage - Laundry - Surveys, 1937-1955 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage - Legislation, Federal, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Minimum Wage - N.Y.S. Orders in Effect, Publication, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  Oct. 1948
- Minimum Wage - Other States, 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Minimum Wage - Reference Material, 1945-1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade - N.Y.S. Industrial Commissioner Contains publication, case, 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade - N.Y.S. Industrial Commissioner - Cases, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade - Report, correspondence, speech, 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage - Restaurant -, 1944-1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage - Restaurant - Hearings, 1947-1957 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage - Restaurant - Report and Recommendations, 1938-1947 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Minimum Wage - Restaurant - Surveys, 1938-1952 (Box 33A, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade, 1957 (Box 33A, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade - Hearings, 1945-1956 (Box 33A, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade - Reports and Recommendations, 1945-1947 (Box 33A, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage - Retail Trade - Surveys, 1947-1955 (Box 33A, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage Bill 'Model' - U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Standards and Women's Bureau, 1957 (Box 33A, Folder 6)
- National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1954-1959 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- National Association of Social Workers, New York Chapter, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- National Child Labor Committee, 1952-1960 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- National Consumers League, Minutes, correspondence, reports of State Leagues, 1944-1946 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- National Consumers League - Bulletin, 1944-1946 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- National Consumer's League, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- National Consumers League, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  Bulletin and newsletter
- National Consumers League, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Statements, release
- National Consumers League, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- National Consumers League, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- National Consumers League, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  Minutes, statements, bulletins
- National Consumers League, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  Minutes, bulletins
- National Consumers League, 1945-1955 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  Miscellaneous Publications
- National Consumers League - Legislative Action, 1945-1950 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- National Consumers League - Bulletin, 1945-1959 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- National Consumers League - Annual Meeting and Conference, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  Dec-58
- National Consumers League - Correspondence (Magee), 1948-1950 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- National Consumers League - Correspondence (Magee), 1951-1953 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- National Consumers League - Correspondence (Magee), 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- National Consumers League - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- National Consumers League - Equal Rights Amendment, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- National Consumers League - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1945-1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- National Consumers League - Membership List - N.Y.C., 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- National Consumers League - Material on Humphrey Sub-Committee Hearings on Migratory Labor in American Agriculture, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- National Consumers League - Migrant Labor Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Includes Reports from Washington
- National Consumers League - Minutes of Board Meetings, 1951-1956 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- National Consumers League - Press Releases, 1951-1958 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- National Consumers League - Questionnaire re Program, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- National Consumers League, 1951-1959 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Resolutions and Policy Statements
- National Consumers League - Committee for Research and Education, Inc. Publications, 1955-1957 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- National Council of Churches - Division of Home Missions, 1953-1960 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  Correspondence
- National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor, 1950-1960 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- National Housing Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- National Sharecroppers Fund, 1955-1959 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  Reports, testimony, correspondence
- National Urban League, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- New Jersey, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- New Jersey Consumers League - Correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 36, Folder 15)